

Nguyen Khoa Minh Nhan

109/3E, Street Thanh Xuan 22, Ward Thanh Xuan, District 12, HCM City, Vietnam

८ (84) 978004319 **☑** nkmnhan@gmail.com **%** https://github.com/nkmnhan

SUMMARY

Senior Software Engineer with 4 years in analysis, design, development, testing, and implementation of various Internet-based, Windows-based applications. I can do BackEnd, Font-End, DevOps, especially my strength server-side. I have over 2 years of experience developing websites and most of them I use Microsoft technologies and some popular JavaScript such as Vuejs and Reactjs. I can work independently or teamwork, ability R&D new technology solving the problem. I have a hobby of researching and writing programming examples.

Blog: https://www.c-sharp.vn/

GitHub: https://github.com/nkmnhan/

My blog and GitHub are storage all my experience, knowledge on it, you can access there and explore about me.

HIGHLIGHTS

- 4+ years in the software development industry.
- Proficient in C#, .Net Core
- Good knowledge of HTML, SCSS, ASP .NET, Web API, WPF, PowerShell
- Good knowledge of MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL
- Experience in Windows OS, Linux OS
- Experience in using a variety of IT management tools such as Git and SVN.
- 1+ year experience in Kubernetes, Docker, Docker Compose
- Research and learn new technologies in a short time
- Conquer the new technology trend always

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages: C#
- Frontend: Javascript, HTML/CSS, SCSS, Vuejs, Reactjs, Bootstrap
- Web Services/Web API: RESTful, Web API, gRPCEM NANC
- Operating System: Windows, Linux.
- Frameworks: .NET Framework, .NET Core, ASP.NET MVC, Entity framework
- Programming Tools: Microsoft Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code
- Database: MS SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Source Control: Git, SVN
- Cloud Platform: Azure- Docker, Docker compose, Kubernetes, CI/CD
- Identity server 4, OKTA Authentication

EDUCATION

University of Information Technology (UIT)

Bachelor of Information Technology

EXPERIENCE

Lowell - NASH TECH Limited

Senior Software Engineer

CLP Team is building the microservices system for the client from Europe. The system is made based on a microservices architecture, modern technologies as .Net Core 3.x for developing backend, VueJs for developing front-end, PostgreSQL for restoring the database, gRPC is the main protocol communication between service

Jan-2019 - Present

together and applying Kubernetes for managing containerized, Azure cloud for deployment environment.

Main responsibilities:

- R&D new technology to help improve the performance of the exchange system
- Build and manage the identity provider
- Setup and implement Docker
- Building the project structure
- Make the detailed designs for assigned tasks
- Write code based on detailed designs and Functional/Requirement Specifications
- Perform a full unit test on the assigned tasks
- Implement unit test
- Incident and bug fixing

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET CORE, REST API, gRPC, Identity Server 4, VueJs, HTML5, RabbitMQ, Azure Service Bus, Kubernetes, Docker.

Open University Open Create - NASH TECH Limited

Nov 2018 - Jan 2019

Software Engineer

Open Create (OC) is a microservices project for Open University in the UK to build innovative, engaging online learning activities for our students and will transform the learning experience, transforming static printed learning materials into dynamic learning experiences, increasing levels of student engagement, and promoting the development and use of digital study skills.

Main responsibilities:

- Make the detailed designs for assigned tasks
- Write code based on detailed designs and Functional/Requirement Specifications
- Perform full unit test on the assigned tasks
- Implement unit test
- Incident and bug fixing

Technologies: Microsoft Azure Cloud, .NET, Angular 2, CSS/HTML

Dimensions - Orion forecast - NASH TECH Limited

Jul 2018 - Nov 2018

Software Engineer

Dimensions is an e-commerce project (Blue Martini) which is provided to Clients with a functional and stable platform to place and manage orders in Twin Hill's e-commerce system.

Main responsibilities:

- Make the detailed designs for assigned tasks
- Write code based on detailed designs and Functional/Requirement Specifications
- Perform full unit test on the assigned tasks
- Implement unit test
- Incident and bug fixing

Technologies: ASP.NET MVC, Azure Service Bus, WinForm

MCS - NGR - Hitachi Consulting Vietnam

Mar 2018 - May 2018

Software Engineer

Develop EI for semi-factory using IBM VTAP framework, SmartTCS and SiView MM / SM for a customer in Singapore

Main responsibilities:

- Analyze process flowDevelop and maintain the MCS system
- Execute testing
- Support build and release the package to customer

Technologies: Groovy, VB.NET language, VTAP framework, SmartTCS, CyberSIM(EI toolkit of GCS)

SOITEC SP1 - Hitachi Consulting Vietnam

Dec 2017 - Mar 2018

Software Engineer

MCS is an ODC project. It provides NGR equipment the interface for equipment-to-host data communications. Via this interface, the host software can control and monitor the equipment such as: start and stop processing, collect measurement data, change variables, select recipe for processing, etc ...

Main responsibilities:

- Analysis process flowDevelop and maintain MCS system
- Execute testing
- Support build and release package to customer

Technologies: GroovyC#, WPF, WCF, CyberSIM(EI toolkit of GCS)

MyCIM 4.0 - Hitachi Consulting Vietnam

Oct 2017 - Dec 2017

Software Engineer

This is a semiconductor project based on IBM Siview SiView.It develops a Material Management client to manage the process of equipment in systems (MES, SPC, iFab) of semiconductor factories in Chengdu China.

Main responsibilities:

- Requirement analysis based on SEMI Standard
- Design data model for Material Management client

Technologies: DB Designer

NADAE - ECACS - Hitachi Consulting Vietnam

Jul 2016 - Oct 2017

Software Engineer

.Net Adaptive Distributed Application Environment (NADAE)NADAE is a rapidly distributed application development framework. The NADAE includes UI framework and Middleware components, which manage communication between services, package deployment, monitoring, exception handling, and data access.

Equipment Controller Application Common Solution (ECACS)ECACS provides solutions to manage Recipes and Substrate Layouts following SEMI-standard, including Recipe and Substrate Layout design, data management.

Main responsibilities:

- Develop ECACS system
- Support testing

Technologies: C#, WPF, MySQL, XML, Windows PowerShell